branch.com 2013-12-28

# None

Effective Date: August 13, 2012

Last Updated Date: August 13, 2012

This Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference into the Branch Terms of Use  The term “ Branch ,” “ we ,” and “ us ” includes Branch Media, Inc. and our affiliates and subsidiaries.  The Privacy Policy explains how Branch may:

  1. collect,
  2. use, and
  3. disclose

information we obtain through the “Branch Service.”

The “ Branch Service ” means any website, mobile application, or Internet service under the control of Branch Media, Inc., whether partial or otherwise, in connection with providing an online platform for Branch’s services.

“ Personal Information ” means information that alone or when in combination with other information may be used to readily identify, contact, or locate you, such as: name, address, email address, or phone number.  We do not consider Personal Information to include information that has been anonymized so that it does not allow a third party to easily identify a specific individual.

The Branch Service Collects Your Information

We collect Personal Information when you:

  1. register to use the Branch Service;
  2. log in with social networking credentials; and
  3. communicate with us or other users using the Branch Service.  

We also collect information, such as anonymous usage statistics, by using cookies, server logs, and other similar technology as you use the Branch Service.

Personal Information Collection.   You must register to use the Branch Service.  To register, you may need to provide Personal Information, such as your name, username, password, and email address.  You may also provide other optional information.

We collect Personal Information from the social media website when you use your social media credentials to log into the Site.  For example, when you log in with your Facebook credentials, we may collect the Personal Information you have made publicly available in Facebook, such as your name, profile picture, and friend list.  We may also obtain other information with your permission.

Using the Branch Service.   We collect information you post through the Branch Service.  For example, when you interact with other users through conversations, the Branch Service will collect the information you provide in such postings, including any Personal Information.  Branch is not responsible for privacy practices of the other users to whom you provide information.

Customer Support.   We may collect Personal Information through your communications with our customer-support team.  

Location Information from Your Mobile Device.   We may collect and store your location information if you enable your mobile device to send it to us.  Collection of this information may improve the provision of the Branch Service.

Cookies, Automatic Data Collection, and Related Technologies.   The Branch Service collects and stores information that is generated automatically as you use it, including your preferences and anonymous usage statistics.

When you visit the Branch Service, we and our third-party service providers receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, and from cookies and similar technology.  Cookies are small text files placed in visitors’ computer browsers to store their preferences.  Most browsers allow you to block and delete cookies.  However, if you do that, the Branch Service may not work properly.

By using the Branch Service, you are authorizing us to gather, parse, and retain data related to the provision of the Branch Service.

How Branch Uses Your Information

We use Personal Information to

  1. facilitate and improve the Branch Service; and
  2. communicate with you.

We do not rent, sell, or share Personal Information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies for their direct marketing purposes, unless we have your permission.  We may use other information, such as your interests, to deliver content to you that may be of interest to you.

We may use aggregate information for any purpose, including for marketing purposes.

Internal and Service-Related Usage.   We use information, including Personal Information, for internal and service-related purposes only and may provide it to third parties to allow us to facilitate the Branch Service.  We may use and retain any data we collect to provide and improve our services.

Communications.   We may send email to the email address you provide to us to verify your account and for informational and operational purposes, such as account management, customer service, or system maintenance.

Displaying to Other Users.   As you use the Branch Service, you will be able to interact with other users and they will be able to see some information, including Personal Information, about you, such as your name, profile photograph, and biographical information.

Marketing.   We do not rent, sell, or share Personal Information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies for their direct marketing purposes, unless we have your permission.  We may use and allow access to other data collected by the Branch Service to enable the delivery of online advertising on the Branch Service, or otherwise facilitate transmittal of content and information that may be useful, relevant, valuable or otherwise of interest to you.

Aggregate Data.   We may anonymize and aggregate data collected through the Branch Service and use it for any purpose.

Branch May Disclose Your Information

We may share your information:

  1. with our third-party service providers;
  2. with search engines and similar services;
  3. to comply with legal obligations;
  4. to protect and defend our rights and property; and
  5. with your permission.

We Use Vendors and Service Providers.   We may share any information we receive with vendors and service providers retained in connection with the provision of the Branch Service.

Social Networking and Other Websites.   The Branch Service may allow you to share information, including Personal Information, with social networking websites, such as Facebook and Twitter.  We do not share your Personal Information with them unless you direct the Branch Service to share it.  Their use of the information will be governed by their privacy policies, and you may be able to modify your privacy settings on their websites.

Search Engines.   Personal Information, such as your name, profile photograph, and biographical information may be accessible via search engines or similar services.  

As Required By Law and Similar Disclosures .  We may access, preserve, and disclose your Personal Information, other account information, and content if we believe doing so is required by law or if those actions are reasonably necessary to:

  1. comply with legal process, such as a court order or subpoena;
  2. enforce this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use;
  3. respond to claims that any content violates the rights of third parties;
  4. respond to your requests for customer service;
  5. respond to law enforcement;
  6. investigate and prevent unauthorized transactions or other illegal activities; or
  7. protect our or others’ rights, property, or personal safety.

Merger, Sale, or Other Asset Transfers.   If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, financing due diligence, reorganization, bankruptcy, receivership, sale of company assets, or transition of service to another provider, your information may be sold or transferred as part of such a transaction.  We cannot control how such entities may use or disclose such information.

We may also disclose your Personal Information with your permission.

Security of Your Information

We take steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  Unfortunately, the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide to us.

By using the Branch Service or providing Personal Information to us, you agree that we may communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of the Branch Service.  If we learn of a security system’s breach, we may attempt to notify you electronically by posting a notice on the Branch Service or sending an email to you.

Children’s Privacy

We do not knowingly collect information from children under 13 and we do not want it.  We will take steps to delete it if we learn we have collected it.

Branch does not knowingly collect, maintain, or use Personal Information from children under 13 years of age, and no part of the Branch Service is directed to children under the age of 13.  If you learn that your child has provided us with Personal Information without your consent, then you may alert us at privacy@branch.com.  If we learn that we have collected any Personal Information from children under 13, we will promptly take steps to delete such information and terminate the child’s account.

International users

By using the Branch Service, you will transfer data to the United States.

By choosing to visit the Branch Service or otherwise provide information to us, you agree that any dispute over privacy or the terms contained in this Privacy Policy will be governed by the law of the state of New York and the adjudication of any disputes arising in connection with Branch or the Branch Service will be in accordance with the [link to Terms of Use ].

If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use, please note that you are agreeing to the transfer of your information to the United States and processing globally. By providing your information you consent to any transfer and processing in accordance with this Policy.

UPDATE YOUR INFORMATION OR POSE A QUESTION OR SUGGESTION

If you would like to update or correct any information that you have provided to us through your use of the Branch Service or otherwise, or if you have suggestions for improving this Privacy Policy, please send an email to privacy@branch.com .

CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY AND PRACTICES

We may revise this Privacy Policy, so review it periodically.

Before we broaden our use of Personal Information beyond what is stated in this Privacy Policy, we will make reasonable efforts to provide notice and obtain consent as required by law.

Posting of Revised Privacy Policy.   We will post any adjustments to the Privacy Policy on this web page, and the revised version will be effective when it is posted.  If you are concerned about how your information is used, bookmark this page and read this Privacy Policy periodically.

New Uses of Personal Information.   From time to time, we may desire to use Personal Information for uses not previously disclosed in our Privacy Policy.  If our practices change regarding previously collected Personal Information in a way that would be materially less restrictive than stated in the version of this Privacy Policy in effect at the time we collected the information, we will make reasonable efforts to provide notice and obtain consent to any such uses as may be required by law.

Contact Information

Branch Media, Inc.

220 East 23rd St. #601

New York NY 10010
